<Tasks>
  <GetItem>
    <ItemId Value="2879991660"/>
    <!-- Can be found in the URL of your workshop item -->
  </GetItem>
  <UpdateItem>
    <ModuleFolder Value="D:\develop\src\RTSCamera\source\package\RTSCamera\"/>
    <!-- A direct path of your module -->
    <ItemDescription Value="
RTS Camera from original creator

Main features:
Free camera mode allows you to give orders in the sky, as if you are playing Total War series.
You can control a teammate to continue fight and issue orders if you are down in battle.
In hideout you can fast forward and let troops fight automatically.

For latest RTS Command: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2879991827
For compatible Battle Mini Map: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2876503777

Save compatibility:
This mod won&apos;t read/write anything from/into your save, so you can feel free to enable or uninstall this mod at any time.


Usage:
Press F10 to toggle free camera mode. The camera movement range is determined by scouting and tactics skill level.
Press E to lock to a unit when the camera is not locking to one.
Press E to control the unit that the camera is locking to.

Press L to open config menu during battles.
Set the &quot;Timing of Control Ally After Death&quot; option to Always to automatically control your teammate after you are down, to avoid your troops automatically charging or following AI's order.

Hotkeys:
F10  -    Toggle free camera mode
E      -    Let the camera lock to a unit, or control the unit that the camera is locking to.
L      -    Open the config menu.
All the hotkeys can be changed in config menu.

Troubleshooting
If there're a lot of &quot;text with id xxxxx doesn't exist&quot;:
    If you enabled Realm of Thrones, please move RTS Camera and Command System above it. As version 6.2 of Realm of Thrones, there's a bug in its file that causes all the mods below it cannot load text correctly.

Feedback or suggestion
Feel free to comment below or send email to lizhenhuan1019@outlook.com

links:
Nexusmods: https://www.nexusmods.com/mountandblade2bannerlord/mods/355
source code: https://github.com/lzh-mb-mod/RTSCamera"/>
    <ChangeNotes Value="" />
    <!-- Insert patch notes -->
    <Tags>
      <!-- You can use the following tags: -->
      <!-- Type: Graphical Enhancement, Map Pack, Partial Conversion, Sound, Total Conversion, Troops, UI, Utility, Weapons and Armour -->
      <!-- Setting: Native, Antiquity, Dark Ages, Medieval, Musket Era, Modern, Sci-Fi, Fantasy, Oriental, Apocalypse, Other -->
      <!-- Game Mode: Singleplayer, Multiplayer -->
      <!-- Compatible Version: e1.9.0, v1.0.0,... The currently available versions can be found at the Steam Workshop "Browse by Tag" section -->
      <Tag Value="UI"/>
      <Tag Value="AI"/>
      <Tag Value="Singleplayer"/>
      <Tag Value="v1.2.12" />
    </Tags>
  </UpdateItem>
</Tasks>