<Tasks>
  <GetItem>
    <ItemId Value="3596693285"/>
    <!-- Can be found in the URL of your workshop item -->
  </GetItem>
  <UpdateItem>
    <ModuleFolder Value="D:\develop\src\RTSCamera\source\package\net472\RTSCamera.CommandSystem\"/>
    
    <!-- A direct path of your module -->
    <ItemDescription Value="RTS Camera Command System part from original creator

Only compatible with beta v1.3.2. For other versions:
v1.2.12: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2879991827
v1.3.0/v1.3.1: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3570723963
v1.3.2: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3596693285

Dependency:
Do not require any of ButterLib/MCM/UIExtenderEx.

Please also subscribe RTS Camera here for complete experience: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3570706807

Reworked the command system in the base game.
Order Queue: Allows to add order to queue to let troops execute orders one by one. For example, move along a given path and then shooting/charging.
Allows your formation attack one of the enemy formation by middle clicking on enemy units.
Allows you to select your formation using mouse.
Fixed issues of formation width and unit spacing in the base game.


For latest RTS Camera: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2879991660
For compatible Battle Mini Map: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2876503777

Save compatibility:
This mod won&apos;t read/write anything from/into your save, so you can feel free to enable or uninstall this mod at any time.


Usage:
Please enable &quot;RTS Camera&quot; and &quot;RTSCamera.CommandSystem&quot; in launcher.
For complete usage: https://github.com/lzh-mb-mod/RTSCamera/blob/master/README.md
Hold Shift and give orders to add orders to queue. Your troops will execute them one by one.
If you move/turn multiple formations at the same time, their relative positions/directions will be locked.
Click middle mouse button on the enemy formation to make your formation attack it.
Click middle mouse button on your formation to select it.
The attacked enemy formation will be highlighted with red outline when you open command panel.
Your attacked formation will be highlighted with dark blue outline when you open command panel.
Your selected formation will be highlighted with green outline when you open command panel.

Press L to open config menu during battles.

Hotkeys:
Shift                      -  Hold to add order to queue when giving orders.
Ctrl                       -  Hold to lock formation widths while dragging on the ground.
Alt                        -  Hold to cancel formation locking during movement or turning.
Click mouse middle button  -  Select/Attack formation.
Hold Alt + Click mouse middle button - Attack enemy formation without interrupting previous movement orders
L                          -    Open the config menu.
All the hotkeys can be changed in config menu.

Troubleshooting
If there&apos;re a lot of &quot;text with id xxxxx doesn&apos;t exist&quot;:
    If you enabled Realm of Thrones, please move RTS Camera and Command System above it. As version 6.2 of Realm of Thrones, there&apos;s a bug in its file that causes all the mods below it cannot load text correctly.

Feedback or suggestion
Feel free to comment below or send email to lizhenhuan1019@outlook.com

links:
Nexusmods: https://www.nexusmods.com/mountandblade2bannerlord/mods/355
source code: https://github.com/lzh-mb-mod/RTSCamera
"/>
    <ChangeNotes Value="" />
    <!-- Insert patch notes -->
    <Tags>
      <!-- You can use the following tags: -->
      <!-- Type: Graphical Enhancement, Map Pack, Partial Conversion, Sound, Total Conversion, Troops, UI, Utility, Weapons and Armour -->
      <!-- Setting: Native, Antiquity, Dark Ages, Medieval, Musket Era, Modern, Sci-Fi, Fantasy, Oriental, Apocalypse, Other -->
      <!-- Game Mode: Singleplayer, Multiplayer -->
      <!-- Compatible Version: e1.9.0, v1.0.0,... The currently available versions can be found at the Steam Workshop "Browse by Tag" section -->
      <Tag Value="UI"/>
      <Tag Value="AI"/>
      <Tag Value="Singleplayer"/>
      <Tag Value="v1.3.4" />
      <Tag Value="v1.3.5" />
      <Tag Value="v1.3.6" />
      <Tag Value="v1.3.7" />
    </Tags>
  </UpdateItem>
</Tasks>